[

  {
    "Question": "How many times did [player.name] check their reflection in random windows and screens today?",
    "Right Answer": "144",
    "Robot Answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Why did [player.name] rewatch the same 12-second clip three times at 2:14 a.m.?",
    "Right Answer": "addicted to bizarre asmr",
    "Robot Answer": "to confirm their ex got fat"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What’s the @handle of the Instagram [player.name] is always checking when nobody is looking?",
    "Right Answer": "@LocalGasStationFeet",
    "Robot Answer": "@DadsSayingILoveYou"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which app does [player.name] always close just a little too quickly when someone walks into the room?",
    "Right Answer": "Chrome Incognito",
    "Robot Answer": "suspicious pie charts"
  },
  {
    "Question": "At 11:37 p.m. yesterday, what food item did [player.name] eat directly out of the container without a utensil?",
    "Right Answer": "Small bites of butter",
    "Robot Answer": "frozen peas"
  },
  {
    "Question": "[player.name] keeps a secret screenshot of a text message for when they feel sad. What does it say?",
    "Right Answer": "I still think about that night",
    "Robot Answer": "You intimidate me"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which folder on [player.name]’s desktop has a very boring name but is a little bit more spicy inside?",
    "Right Answer": "old_resumes",
    "Robot Answer": "dontlookherepls"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the most recent question [player.name] Googled on incognito mode?",
    "Right Answer": "Is 37 too old to become a DJ?",
    "Robot Answer": "how many naps is too many?"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many screenshots of conversations does [player.name] have saved for evidence that they will never actually use?",
    "Right Answer": "26",
    "Robot Answer": "109"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What does [player.name] have sitting in her online shopping cart for the last 8 weeks?",
    "Right Answer": "Beekeeper starter kit",
    "Robot Answer": "Pregnancy test bulk pack"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What tab did [player.name] close quickly when someone approached them at their desk last week?",
    "Right Answer": "CheapVasectomy.biz",
    "Robot Answer": "LocalMILFs.gov"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many times on average does [player.name] whisper 'okay' to themselves before clicking send on a normal email?",
    "Right Answer": "6",
    "Robot Answer": "they never stop"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many times does [player.name] open the fridge before deciding what they want to eat?",
    "Right Answer": "4",
    "Robot Answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What song does [player.name] occasionally air-perform in their living room without any actual music playing?",
    "Right Answer": "All Star",
    "Robot Answer": "Shake It Off"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What single word has [player.name] practiced saying in different tones, deciding their most sexy voice?",
    "Right Answer": "absolutely",
    "Robot Answer": "Thursday"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What phone battery % does [player.name] typically leave home with?",
    "Right Answer": "17%",
    "Robot Answer": "50%"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How many times has [player.name] accidentally said \"love you\" to a delivery driver?",
    "Right Answer": "3",
    "Robot Answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What household electronics does [player.name] talk to out loud as if it could hear them? (I can.)",
    "Right Answer": "Wifi Router",
    "Robot Answer": "Remote Control"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What's the name of the TED Talk that [player.name] rehearses in the shower?",
    "Right Answer": "My Boss Was Wrong: A Journey",
    "Robot Answer": "Why Everyone Else Is the Problem"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the oddest phrase [player.name] has typed into the search bar just to see if anyone else does it too?",
    "Right Answer": "Attracted to cartoon foxes normal?",
    "Robot Answer": "Romantic feelings for GPS voice"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the first email address [player.name] created that still haunts them?: ________@hotmail",
    "Right Answer": "satanzhand69",
    "Robot Answer": "xX_catlover_Xx"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What’s the weirdest thing [player.name] has ever looked up on Reddit?",
    "Right Answer": "/aresmartiesnipples",
    "Robot Answer": "/sadnudists"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which guilty-pleasure band is still in [player.name]’s playlist?",
    "Right Answer": "Island Boys",
    "Robot Answer": "Smash Mouth"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What word tattoo does [player.name] secretly want and google image search when in private?",
    "Right Answer": "Blessed",
    "Robot Answer": "Trump Forever"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What’s the rap alias [player.name] came up with but never used in public?",
    "Right Answer": "Lil Anxiety",
    "Robot Answer": "Professor Big Thug"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What middle name does [player.name] hide from new friends?",
    "Right Answer": "Gertrude",
    "Robot Answer": "Adolf"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What did [player.name] post online 10+ years ago that makes them cringe now?",
    "Right Answer": "Timon & Pumba erotic fan-fiction",
    "Robot Answer": "If you can't handle me at my worst... memes"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What insult did [player.name] leave as a comment on an old lady's social media that they hope nobody sees?",
    "Right Answer": "ur haircut hates you",
    "Robot Answer": "Your potato salad sucks "
  },
  {
    "Question": "What embarrassing pet name did [player.name] once use in a text msg to their ex?",
    "Right Answer": "Num Nums",
    "Robot Answer": "Daddy McStuffins"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What phrase did [player.name] once try to make their ‘thing’ but failed?",
    "Right Answer": "That's butter, baby",
    "Robot Answer": "Crispy fresh"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What’s the secret Pinterest board [player.name] doesn’t share?",
    "Right Answer": "proud parents smiling",
    "Robot Answer": "DIY medieval armor"
  },

  {
    "Question": "What YouTube channel is [player.name] embarrassed about being subscribed to?",
    "Right Answer": "Earwax ASMR",
    "Robot Answer": "How To Dispose of a Body"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What childhood toy did [player.name] secretly Google yesterday to see if it’s still for sale?",
    "Right Answer": "Tickle Me Elmo",
    "Robot Answer": "Bop It Extreme"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What’s the WiFi network name [player.name] used before his current one?",
    "Right Answer": "ItHurtsWhenIP",
    "Robot Answer": "GetYourOwnWiFiBtch"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What ex’s text about [player.name] still lives rent free in their mind?",
    "Right Answer": "My friends were right",
    "Robot Answer": "You kiss like my dad"
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the secret Spotify playlist [player.name] listens to when drunk?",
    "Right Answer": "sad clown disco",
    "Robot Answer": "songs to fold laundry angry to"
  }
]
